Jacobs, Arthur Additional Arbitration Papers 6139
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arthur Jacobs Additional Arbitration Papers
1977-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacobs, Arthur
6139
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers.
5819027
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 10, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial; Jacobs, Arthur T.
5819027
- AB Neckwear and Bow Co. New School for Social Research, 1977-1994. (Box 1)
  - AB Neckwear and Bow Co/ ACTWU Locals 250C and 253C, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A.E. Electronics Corp. / International Assn of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, NO. 15, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A.E. Electronics Corp/ International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers Local 431, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abbott UFSD/ Abott School Teachers' Assoc., Secretarial - Clerical Maintenance Unit, NYSUT, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Press Inc./ ACTWU local 1870, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Amoco Oil Co. / Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 7-1, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Apex Metal Co. /IUE local 485, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ardsley Free School / Ardsley Congress of Teachers District BOE, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arlington CSD/ CSEA, Dutchess Co. Educational Local, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Armour Pharmaceutical Co / International Chemical Workers Union, local 498, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ASI-W/P, Inc. / Amalgamated Industrial/and Service workers Union, Local 6 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aurora, City of/ International Assn. of fire fighters, Local 99 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - BandR Children's Overalls/ Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Local 169, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - BandS finishing Inc./ ACTWU Local 169, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - BDJ Contracting Co/ ACTWU local 169, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Babylon Motor Truck Corp/ Amalgamated local 355, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Beacon City School District/ Beacon Teachers Assn., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bender Brothers Sportswear/ ACTWU, joint Board of Shirt, leisurewear, robe, glove and rainwear, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Berkley Cravats Ltd. /ACTWU locals 250c and 253c, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bethlehem, Town of/ Bethlehem PBA, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Boces, Dutchess Co. /Dutchess Co. BOCES Faculty Assn., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - BOCES, Rockland Co /Boces Staff Assn, NYSUT, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Boces, Southern Westchester/ Boces Teachers Assn., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Boces, Suffolk County 1st Supervisor District/ Boces #1 Teachers Assn., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Brasscrafters Inc./ International Assn. of Machinists and Aerospace workers, Dist. Lodge #15, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Brewster CSD/ Brewster Teachers Assn., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bookhatten Transportation Inc./ Local 355, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn Standard Bag Corp. / I.B. of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Union, Local 107, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Building Service Employees Int'l Union, School and Library Emp. Local 74, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Burnside - Graham Ready Mix, Inc./ IBT local 135, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Byram hills School District/ Byram Hills Teachers Assn., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - CandC Haulage Corp./ IBT Local 282, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Caesars Atlantic City/ Local 54 Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Cairo-Durham CSD/ Cairo - Durham Teachers Assn. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Capitol DistrictandRegional Off-track Betting Corp./ AFSCME, Council 66, Local 2055, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Carbrundum Co./ Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers Local 9-490, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Carmel CSD/ Carmel Office Staff Assoc., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Carmel CSD/ Carmel CSEA, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Carmel CSD/ Carmel Paraprofessional Staff Assn., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Carmel CSD/ Carmel Teacher Assistants Assn., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Carmel, town of /Town of Carmel PBA, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Carson Pirie Scott and Co/ Warehouse, mail order, Office, Technical and Professional Employees Union Local 7843, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Catholic Cemeteries of Brooklyn / Seiu Local 365, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cee-Bee Manufacturing/ IBT Local 816, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Central Hudson Gas and Electric/ I.B. of Electrical Workers Locals 320 and 2218, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Central Islip UFSD/ Central Islip Teachers Assn., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - City of Champaign/ AFSCME council 31, local 1690, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Charmer Industries & other Liquor Companies/ Liquor salesmen's Union Local #2 AFL-CIO, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - City Tank Corp/ Int'l Assn. of Machinists, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Clarkstown CSD/ Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1181-1061, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Clarkstown CSD/ CSEA (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Clarkstown CSD/ Clarkstown Teaching Assistants, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Clarkstown CSD BOE/ Clarkstown Teachers Assn., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Classy togs/ ACTWU local 169, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Clearview Gardens 1st 6th Corp./ I.B.T. Local 813, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Coca-Cola Bottling Co. / I.B.T. Local 744, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Connie Sportswear/ ACTWU - Joint Board of Shirt Leisurewear, robe, Glare and Rainwear Workers, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Consolidated Laundries/ Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Consolidation Coal Co. Loveridge #22 Mine/ United Mine Workers of America District #31 Local 9909, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Consolidation Coal Co. United Mine Workers of America Dist. 31 Local 5429, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Cook County/ IBT Local 714, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Cornwall CSD/ Cornwall Teachers Assn., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Croton - Harmon UFSD/ Croton Teachers Assn., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Croton-on-Hudson/ Croton Police Assoc., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Dana Corporation/Unite Locals 250c and 253c, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Debutogs Inc. / ACTWU, Shirtand leisure wear Division NY Joint Board, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Dept. of me Army Rock Island Arsenal/ Nat'l Assn. of Gov't Employees Local B7-68, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Dobbs Ferry UFSD/ Dobbs Ferry Teacher Assn., 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Dominick's finer Foods/ United Food and Commercial Workers Int'l Union. Local 1540, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Dover UFSD/ Dover Wingdale, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Dunleigh Tuxton Corp./ ACTWU - Neckwear and Accessories Division. NY Joint Board, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - E. Trani and Sons Inc. / ACTWU local 169, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - EandM Sportswear/ Brother Fashions/ ACTWU Local 169, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - EW Saybolt and Co/ Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Local 8-337, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Eagle Food Centers, Inc./ INT Local 371, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Eagle Food Centers, store 087/ United Foodand Commercial workers local 1540, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - East Greenbush CSD/ E. Greenbush Secretarial/ Clerical Assn., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - East Ramapo CSD/ NYS Nurses Assn., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Eastchester UFSD/ Eastchester Teachers Assn., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Eastern Air Devices/ International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 243, IUE, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Eastern Associated Coal Corp./ United Mine Workers of America, Dist 31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Elmsford UFSD/ Elmsford Teachers Assn., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Embee Sunshade Co/ RCIA Local 888, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Esquire Junior LTD/ / Local 169 ACTWU, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Eton Chemists/ Retail Drugstore Employees Local 11999 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Town of Fallsburg/ Fallsburg Police Benevolent Assoc., 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Fine liquor shop/ Local 122 Wine and Liquor Store Employees, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Fire Islander Manufacturing/ ACTWU 169, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Fixmobile Inc,/ IBT Local 966, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Flatbush General Hospital/ Registered Nurses Assn., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Flexsteel Industries/ United Steelworkers of America, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Florida UFSD/ Florida Teachers Assn., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Franbe Industries/ Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Novelty Workers ACTWU 169, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Franklin Body/ I.B.T., Local 810, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Freeport UFSD #9 / CSEA, Custodial, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - French and Polyclinic Medical School and Health Center/ Hotel and Allied Service Employees union, Local 144, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Fujitsu Business Communication Systems/ I.B. Electrical Workers Local 336, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - GandB Packing Co/ Local 3128 UBCandJ of America, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Garrison UFSD Boe/ Garrison Teachers Assn. NYSUT, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - GenCorp/ United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 466, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - General Bronze Corporation/ IABSand OIW Local 455, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - General Foods Manufacturing Corp. / Local 348 United Food and Commercial Workers, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Germantown CSD/ Germantown Teachers Assn., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Village of Goshen/ CSEA Local 836, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Greenburgh CSD No. 7 BOE/ Greenburgh Central 7 Administrative Org., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Greenburgh CSD #7 BOE/ Greensburgh Teachers Federation Local 1788 AFT, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Greensburgh 11 UFSD B.O.E. / Greensburgh 11 Federation of Teachers AFT Local 1532, 1978-1991 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Greenwich, Town of/ Local 136, Laborers International Union of N. America, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Greenwood Lake UFSD/ Greenwood Lake Teachers Assoc., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - HandK Knit Garments/ Shirt and Leisurewear Division NY Joint Board, ACTWU, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - HandM Manufacturing/ ACTWU Local 169, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Haeger Potteries of Macomb/ Glass, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers Unt'l Union Local 340, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Haldane CSDBOE/ Haldane Faculty Assn., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Haldane CSD/ William Mevante, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Harcros Pigments Inc/ I.B. Painters and Allied Trades, Local 1850, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Hauppauge UFSD/ Hauppauge Teachers Assn., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Hawthorne Cedar Knolls School UFSD #3/ AFT, Local 1169, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Hempstead BOE, / Hempstead Classroom Teachers Assoc., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Hempstead, Village of/ PBA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Hermark Knitwear Corp./ ACTWU - Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, glove and Rainwear workers Union, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Herricks UFSD/ Herricks Teachers' Assn., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Hertz Corp. /IBT Local 813, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Hicksand Otis Prints Inc. /ACTWU local 169, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Highland CSD/ Highland Teachers Assn., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Hilton Davis Co. / Oil, Chemicals and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-406, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Hoeganaes Corp/ IBT local 676, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Holiday Togs/ ACTWU Local 169, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Hopewell Valley Regional BOE/ Hopewell Valley Administrators and Supervisors Assn., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Hospital for Joints Diseases Orthopedic Institute/ Hospital and Healthcare Employees District 1199, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Howard Creations/ ACTWU, Neckwears and Accessories Division, NY Joint Board, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Hyde Park Teachers Assn/ Hyde Park CSD, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Hy-Matic Manufacturing/ International Molders and Allied Workers Union Local 262, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Immigration & Naturalization Service, Dept. of justice/ A.F.G.E, Local 1917, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Individualized Shirt Co. / Unite, Shirt and Leisurewear Division, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Irvington, Village of/ CSEA, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - I.S. North/ Unite, Shirt and Leisurewear division, NY Joint Board, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - J.L. Treadway Trucking Co./ United Mine Workers of America, district 31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Jack & Jill Togs Inc./ ACTWU Local 169 Washable ClothingSportswear and Novelty Workers, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - JARCO Garment Co/ ACTWU 169, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Jayel Childrens wear Manufacturing corp. / ACTWU local 169, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Jefferson Smurfit Corp/ United Paperworkers International Union Local 1215, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Jefferson Smurfit Corp/ Communication union Local 415-S, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Jewel Food Stores/ United Food and Commercial Workers Local 881, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Jodell Garment Inc. / ACTWU local 169, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Johar Chemists, Inc. dba Printers Prescription cntr. / Allied Trades council, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Johnson Controls Inc/ IBT Local 710, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Julie Ann. / ACTWU 169, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Jupola Fashions Corp./ ACTWU local 169, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Keys and Lockwood Inc. / ACTWU, Neckwear and Accessories Divison, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Kingston, City of/ Kingston Patrolmen's Benevolent Assn., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Kingston Water Board/ AFSCME Council 66 Local 750, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Kord's Ambulance Service/ ILGWU - Warehouse and Office Workers Local 512, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - LaGuardia Hospital/ Hotel, Hospital, Nursing home and Allied Services Union SETU Local 144, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Label Processing Corp/ International Assn. of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local lodge 2067 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Lakeland CSD/ Lakeland Federation of Teachers, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Lebern Enterprises/ ACTWU 169, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Long Beach, City of/ Long Beach Patrolmen's Benevolent Assn., 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Lozier Corp/ Sheet Metal Workers International Assoc. Local No. 3, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Mahopac Boe/ CSEA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Mahopac CSD/ IBT, Local 456, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Mahopac CSD/ Mahopac Teachers Assoc - Teaching Assistants Chapter, NYSUT, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Village of Mamaroneck/ Police Benevolent Association, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Mamaroneck UFSD/ Mamaroneck Teachers Assn., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Manchester Regional high School Boe/ Manchester Administrators Association, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Marboro Books/ Distributive Workers of America District 65, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Marvier Fashions/ ACTWU 169, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Marilyn Togs/ ACTWU 169, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Masback Inc. / I.B.T. Local 850, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Master Craft/ ACTWU local 169, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Match Points Fashions / ACTWU, Local 169, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Meadow Sportswear / Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, Local 169, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Ireco, Inc. / United Steelworkers of America, local13226, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Menorah Home & Hospital/ Hotel, Hospital and Nursing Home Union, Local 144, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Neralva Fashions / Unite 169, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Merck and Company / Chemand Atomic Workers International Local 8-575, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Mid-Island Electric Supply/ IBEW local 1922, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - City of Middletown/ Orange Co. Local CSEA, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Middletown Enlarged City/ Middletown Teachers Assn. School District, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Millbrook CSD/ Millbrook Teacher Assoc. (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company/ Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International/ Union Local 8-760, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Mongru Neckwear/ ACTWU Locals 250c/ 253c, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Monroe-Woodbury CSD/ CSEA Local 836, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Monticello, Village of/ Tri-county NY Public Employees Local 750 AFSCME, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Moonlight Fashions/ Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Local 169, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Morley Shirt Co. Inc., /ACTWU, Shirt and leisurewear Division, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Mt. Pleasant Central Schools/ Mt. Pleasant Teachers Assoc., 1986-1998 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Mt. Pleasant Cottage/ Mt. Pleasant Teachers Assn. UFSD, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Morris Paper Board Division of Berles Carton Co. Inc./ United Paperworkers International Union local 300, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - M.R. Sportswear/ ACTWU local 169, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Mustang Sportswear Inc./ ACTWU local 169 Bradley Michele Inc., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Nanuet BoE/ CSEA, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Nanuet UFSD/ Nanuet Teachers Assn., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - New School for Social Research/ IBT Local 1518, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 193)
- New Paltz CSD Yorktown CSD; Correspondence, 1977-1994. (Box 2)
  - New Paltz Central School District/ New Paltz United Teachers, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - New Rochelle, City of/ New Rochelle Police Superior Officer Assn., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - New Rochelle, City of/ UFFA, Local 273, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New Windsor, Town of/ Patrolmen's Benevolent Assoc., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - New Windsor, Town of/ CSEA Orange Co. Local 836, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - New York, City of/ Service Employees International local 246, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New York State, Dept. of Correctional Services/ AFSCME cl. 82 5189-4199, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - NYS D.E.C./ AFSCME cl. 82, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - NYS Parks, Recreation, Historic Preservation Dept./ AFSCME Cl.82, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NYS Thruway Authority/ IB7 local 72, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - New York State Unified Court System/ Suffolk Co. Court Employees Assn., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Newburgh BOE/ Newburgh Teachers Assn., 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - City of Newburgh/ CSEA local 836, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - City of Newburgh/ International Assoc. of Firefighters, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - City of Newburgh/ Patrolmen's Benevolent Assoc. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Newburn, Town of/ Orange Co. PBA, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - North Salem CSD/ CSEA Local 1000, Food Service Unit, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - North Salem CSD BOE/ North Salem Teachers Assoc. Local 2879, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Northshore CSD BoE/ North Shore Federated Employees, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - North Shore CSD/ North Shore Schools Faculty Assn., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Northeast Program Service Cntr, Bureau of Retirement, Survivors Insurance/ Nat'l council of soc. Sec. Payment Center, Local 1760, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Nyack UFSD/ Nyack Teachers Assn., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - OK Uniform Inc. / ACTWU local 169, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Okaloosa Co. School Board/ Okaloosa Co. Education Assn., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Omaha Standard Inc./ Paper, Allied Industrial, Chem and Energy Workers, Local 7-0795, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Orange Co./ Orange Co. Local 836 CSEA, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Orange Co. / Orange Co. Employees Assn, Local 1000 AFSCME (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Orange County Community College/ Charles Reilly and Chairmen's Assn. of Orange c3 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Orange Co. Comm. College/ Orange Co. Faculty Assn., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Orange Co. Sheriff/ Orange Co. Deputy Sheriff's Assoc., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Orangetown, Town of/ CSEA, Rockland Co. Chapter, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Orangetown, Town of/ Orangetown PBA, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Orangetown and Clarkstown UFSD #4 BoE/ Nyack Teachers Assoc., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Ottaway Newspaper/ Independent Assn. of Publishers Employees, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Pearl River BoE/ Pearl River Teachers Assn., 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Peekskill BoE/ Peekskill Teachers Assn., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - City of Peekskill School District/ Peekskill Faculty Assoc., 1983-1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Peekskill City School Dist./ Peekskill Professional Assn. of Educational Secretaries, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Pennbrook Manufacturing/ ACTWU local 169, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania/ AFSCME, council 13 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of Dept. of Education/ Federation of State Cultural and Educational Professionals, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Peoples Gas Light and Coke Company/ Gas Workers Union Local 18007, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Phoenix Union High/ Phoenix Classified Employee's Assoc., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Phoenix Union High/ Phoenix Classroom Teachers Assoc., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Pine Bush CSD/ Pine Bush Teachers Assn., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Pine Plains CSD no. 1/ Pine Plains Education Assoc., 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Pioneer Watch Case Co./ Int'l Jewelry Workers Union local #1, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Pius XII School, Inc./ Org. of Pius XII Employees, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Plainedge UFSD/ Plainedge Federation of Teachers, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Playboy Neckwear Corp. /ACTWU, Locals 250c and 253c, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Pocantico Hills CSD / Pocantico Hills Teachers Assn., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Polivy Electric/ Industrial Workers of Allied Trade Local 199, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Port Jefferson UFSD no. 6/ Port Jefferson Teachers Assn., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Port Jervis City School Dist/ CSEA, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Port Jervis City School Dist./ Port Jervis Teachers Assn., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Portchester - Rye UFSD BoE/ Port Chester Trachers Assn., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Poughkeepsie City School District BoE/ Poughkeepsie Public School Teachers Assoc., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - PRI Fashions/ Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Novelty Workers local 169, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Putnam Co. Bd. Of Supervisors/ Putnam Co. Deputy Sheriff's Benevolent Assn., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Putnam Valley CSD/ Putnam Valley Federation of Teachers, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Qualigraphics Inc./ Printing Pressmen, Assistants and offset Workers Union #183, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Queens - Long Island Medical Group/ Office and Prof. Employees International Local 153, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Quinn and Boden Inc./ International printing and graphic Communications Union local 183, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - RandP Manufacturing Co./ ACTWU local 169, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Red Hook CSD/ Red Hook Faculty Assn., 1987 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Renco Sportswear/ ACTWU 169, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Revere Aluminum Building Products/ I.B.T. Local 239, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Richfield Knitwear Co./ ACTWY Joint Board Shirt, Leisurewear, Glove, Robe, Rainwear, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Rochester, Town of/ I.B. of Electrical Workers, local 1968, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Rockland County/ Local 823, C1.66, AFSCME (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Rondout Valley Central School/ AFSCME Local 1000, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Rondout Valley CSD/ Rondout Valley Teachers Assoc., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Rush - Presbyterian - St. Luke's Medical Center/ IBT Local 743, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Russell Aives Mills, Ltd./ ACTWU local 169, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Rutgers University/ William Combs - Administrative Professional and Supervisory Personnel, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 75)